(Sheldon:)You're not done with her, are you?
(Leonard:)Our babies will be smart and beautiful.
(Sheldon:)Not to mention imaginary.
- Is Thai food okay with you, Penny?
- Sure.
(Sheldon:)We can't have Thai,
we had Indian for lunch.
(Leonard:)- So?
- They're both curry-based cuisines.
- It would be gastronomically redundant.
(Sheldon:)I can see we're going to have to
spell out everything for this girl.
(Penny:)Any ideas, Raj?
(Howard:)Turn left on Lake Street
and head up to Colorado.
(Howard:)I know a wonderful little sushi bar
that has karaoke.
Oh, that sounds like fun.
[SINGING]
Baby, baby, don't get hooked on me
Oh, baby, baby
Don't get hooked on me
I don't know your odds
in the world as a whole...
(Sheldon:)...but as far as the population of this car
goes, you're a veritable mac daddy.
(Howard(sings):)Baby, don't get hooked on me